Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series C: Group Portraits, September 1937-August 1938., 10605
  - Photo Unit #: C269 Lumbermen from Northwest: John Givulinovich and Wilfred "Idaho" Chapin, Dec 1937; 10727 (Item 11-1002)
  - Photo Unit #: C270 English kitchen at Alcaniz, Dec 1937; 10726 (Item 11-1003)
  - Photo Unit #: C276 Group of Servicio Sanidad [Health] of Lincoln-Washington, Dec 1937; 10725 (Item 11-1004)
  - Photo Unit #: C277 [?] and Harry Noble, Dec 1937; 10724 (Item 11-1005)
  - Photo Unit #: C279 Sound truck, R. Karman [?] and C. Silverman [?], Dec 1937; 10723 (Item 11-1006)
  - Photo Unit #: C281 Nathan Weisenfeld [alias Neil Wesson], Major Robert Merriman, Captain Alfredo Balsa, Dec 1937; 10722 (Item 11-1328)
  - Photo Unit #: C285 Train group going from Ambite to Alcaniz, Dec 1937; 10721 (Item 11-0774)
  - Photo Unit #: C287 Train group going from Ambite to Alcaniz, Dec 1937; 10720 (Item 11-0775)
  - Photo Unit #: C288 Chauffeurs, 15th British [?], Auto Park, Dec 1937; 10719 (Item 11-1007)
  - Photo Unit #: C289 Three Carbonell brothers, Pablo, Victor, Jorge, Dec 1937; 10718 (Item 11-1008)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/23)
  - Photo Unit #: C290 Chauffeurs, "Dusty" Miller, Kaye Alexander, Dec 1937; 10716 (Item 11-1009)
  - Photo Unit #: C293 Louis Secundy, Abraham Lewis, Dec 1937; 10715 (Item 11-1010)
  - Photo Unit #: C298 John Gates (l.), Political Commissar, International Brigade base, Captain Robert Thompson, MacKenzie-Papineau and David Doran, Political Commissar, 15th Brigade, Ambite, Dec 1937; 10714 (Item 11-0776)
  - Photo Unit #: C299 David Doran, Lieutenant Harry Poll, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, General Walter [alias of Karol Swierczewski], Dec 1937; 10713 (Item 11-0777)
  - Photo Unit #: C303 Louis Secundy, Chief of Auto Park, 15th International Brigade, Dec 1937; 10711 (Item 11-0778)
  - Photo Unit #: C304 [?], Joe Taylor and [?], Brigade Scouts, Dec 1937; 10710 (Item 11-1329)
  - Photo Unit #: C306 At Argente, Jan 1938; 10709 (Item 11-1011)
  - Photo Unit #: C307 [?], [?] and Claude Pringle, Dec 1937; 10708 (Item 11-1012)
  - Photo Unit #: C310 Group of Brigade Commissariat, Argente, Jan 1938; 10707 (Item 11-1013)
  - Photo Unit #: C317 At front, E. [?] Teruel, Jan 1938; 10706 (Item 11-1014)
  - Photo Unit #: C319 At Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Teruel Front, Jan 1938; 10705 (Item 11-1015)
  - Photo Unit #: C320 At MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion near [?], Jan 1938; 10703 (Item 11-1016)
  - Photo Unit #: C327 Cubans in the 24th Brigade, Jan 1938; 10702 (Item 11-1017)
  - Photo Unit #: C330 Couriers of 15th Brigade, Jan 1938; 10700 (Item 11-1018)
  - Photo Unit #: C331 Motor cyclists of 15th Brigade, Jan 1938; 10699 (Item 11-1019)
  - Photo Unit #: C333 Jesse Wallach, Samuel Romer, Eugene Nolte of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Jan 1938; 10698 (Item 11-1020)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/29)
  - Photo Unit #: C337 In Teruel, Feb 1938; 10697 (Item 11-0779)
  - Photo Unit #: C338 In Teruel, Feb 1938; 10696 (Item 11-0780)
  - Photo Unit #: C345 Robert Merriman, Earl Browder, Feb 1938; 10695 (Item 11-0781)
  - Photo Unit #: C346 Earl Browder, Vladimir Copic, Feb 1938; 10694 (Item 11-0782)
  - Photo Unit #: C348 Earl Browder and officers of the 15th International Brigade, Feb 1938; 10693 (Item 11-0783)
  - Photo Unit #: C349? Earl Browder and officers of the 15th International Brigade, Feb 1938; 304562 (Item 11-1875A)
  - Photo Unit #: C350 Earl Browder[center] and officers of the 15th International Brigade, Feb 1938; 304563 (Item 11-1865)
  - Photo Unit #: C351 William Oderaka, Robert Minor, Anthony Drossel, Feb 1938; 10692 (Item 11-0784)
  - Photo Unit #: C354 Edward Barsky (l.) and Edward Patterson, MacKenzie-Papineau, after Teruel, Feb 1938; 10691 (Item 11-0785)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/2)
  - Photo Unit #: C355 On the anniversary of their last year in Spain, Feb 1938; 10690 (Item 11-0786)
  - Photo Unit #: C357 After Teruel, Feb 1938; 10689 (Item 11-0787)
  - Photo Unit #: C358 Morris Stamm (l.) and [?], Lincoln-Washington, after Teruel, Feb 1938; 10688 (Item 11-0788)
  - Photo Unit #: C360 Group of Californians in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Agua-viva [?], Feb 1938; 10687 (Item 11-1021)
  - Photo Unit #: C363 Lillian Armstan, nurse, and Norman Dorland, 35th Division Sanidad [Health], Feb 1938; 10686 (Item 11-1022)
  - Photo Unit #: C365 Scene in front of Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Cedrilla, Feb 1938; 10685 (Item 11-1023)
  - Photo Unit #: C366 Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, Feb 1938; 10684 (Item 11-1024)
  - Photo Unit #: C367 Kitchen, Lincoln-Washington, Feb 1938; 10683 (Item 11-0378)
  - Photo Unit #: C368 Eating at Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, Feb 1938; 10682 (Item 11-1025)
  - Photo Unit #: C369 Lincoln-Washington Battalion eating, Feb 1939; 10681 (Item 11-1026)
  - Photo Unit #: C370 Lincoln-Washington Battalion eating, Feb 1938; 10680 (Item 11-1027)
  - Photo Unit #: C371 Paul White of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Feb 1938; 10679 (Item 11-1028)
  - Photo Unit #: C372 Soldiers of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Feb 1938; 10678 (Item 11-1029)
  - Photo Unit #: C373 John Panaszewicz of Lincoln-Washington fortification group, John P. Hunter of Lincoln-Washington Chemical Unit, Feb 1938; 10677 (Item 11-1030)
  - Photo Unit #: C374 Anthony Kerhlicker, Elias (Ilya) Balagurchick, Lincoln-Washington fortification, Feb 1938; 10676 (Item 11-1031)
  - Photo Unit #: C380 Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, Valverde, Mar 1938; 10675 (Item 11-1032)
  - Photo Unit #: C384 South American of Company 2, 59th Battalion, Mar 1938; 10674 (Item 11-1033)
  - Photo Unit #: C385 Machine-Gun group of Company 2, 59th Battalion, Mar 1938; 10673 (Item 11-1034)
  - Photo Unit #: C386 Machine-Gun group of Company 2, 59th Battalion, Mar 1939; 10672 (Item 11-1035)
  - Photo Unit #: C388 Cubans in 59th Battalion, Mar 1938; 10671 (Item 11-1036)
  - Photo Unit #: C393 Dr. Imek Bernstein, Maxim. Lieutenant [?] Biegelman, Mar 1938; 10670 (Item 11-1037)
  - Photo Unit #: C394 Captain Leonard Lamb, Lieutenant William Digges, Mar 1938; 10669 (Item 11-1038)
  - Photo Unit #: C395 Mappers and observers of the Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Mar 1938; 10668 (Item 11-1039)
  - Photo Unit #: C396 Preparing rifles for inspection, Lincoln-Washington, Mar 1938; 10667 (Item 11-0259)
  - Photo Unit #: C397 Preparing rifles for inspection at Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Mar 1938; 10666 (Item 11-1040)
  - Photo Unit #: C398 Preparing rifles for inspection at Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Mar 1938; 10665 (Item 11-1041)
  - Photo Unit #: C399 Greeks in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Mar 1938; 10664 (Item 11-1042)
  - Photo Unit #: C400 Greek Cypriots in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Mar 1938; 10663 (Item 11-1043)
  - Photo Unit #: C401 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion at Valverde, Mar 1938; 10662 (Item 11-1044)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/13)
  - Photo Unit #: C402 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion at Valverde, Mar 1938; 10661 (Item 11-1045)
  - Photo Unit #: C403 Group in Lincoln-Washington Battalion at Valverde, Mar 1938; 10660 (Item 11-1046)
  - Photo Unit #: C406 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion Group, Valverde, Mar 1938; 10659 (Item 11-1330)
  - Photo Unit #: C407 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Valverde [?] [soldiers on ground], 304919 (Item 11-1866)
  - Photo Unit #: C409 Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, Mar 1938; 10658 (Item 11-1047)
  - Photo Unit #: C426 British Battalion office, Valverde; [soldier using a typewriter on the ground], Feb 1938; 10657 (Item 11-1815)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/14)
  - Photo Unit #: C431 Air bomb holes, Mar 1938; 10656 (Item 11-1048)
  - Photo Unit #: C432 Transmissions: Harry Fellman, John Rossen and Harry Perlman, Mar 1938; 10655 (Item 11-1049)
  - Photo Unit #: C441 At work at Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Hijar, Mar 1938; 10654 (Item 11-1050)
  - Photo Unit #: C446 Printing a bulletin, political commissariat at work, Brigade mimeo (2 Spaniards) at Emilio Sanchez (17, killed Baleau) Proper spelling to come soon., Mar 1938; 10653 (Item 11-1331)
  - Photo Unit #: C451 Brigade Runners, Mar 1938; 10652 (Item 11-1051)
  - Photo Unit #: C455 Robert Merriman, Nicolai [?], undated; 10651 (Item 11-1332)
  - Photo Unit #: C456 Spanish cooks of MacKenzie-Papineau, Letux, Mar 1938; 10650 (Item 11-1333)
  - Photo Unit #: C459 Wood for MacKenzie-Papineau kitchen, Letux, Mar 1938; 10649 (Item 11-1052)
  - Photo Unit #: C461 Company 1, MacKenzie-Papineau, Letux [resting in a grove], Mar 1938; 10648 (Item 11-1334)
  - Photo Unit #: C465 Office, 15th Brigade, Mar 1938; 10647 (Item 11-1053)
  - Photo Unit #: C468 Company 3 Headquarters, MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Mar 1938; 10646 (Item 11-1054)
  - Photo Unit #: C469 Company 4, Letux, Mar 1938; 10645 (Item 11-1055)
  - Photo Unit #: C472 Intendencia boys hauling oranges, Alcorisa, Feb 1938; 10644 (Item 11-1056)
  - Photo Unit #: C473 Group from base Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Alcorisa, Feb 1938; 10643 (Item 11-1057)
  - Photo Unit #: C475 Lieutenant Sanchez, Herman (Gabby) Klein, [?], Lieutenant [?] Carmona, Harry Lichter, Eloy Bouha [?], Feb 1938; 10642 (Item 11-0789)
  - Photo Unit #: C484 Ambulance: [?], [?], Murray Nemeroff, Valls, May 1938; 10641 (Item 11-1058)
  - Photo Unit #: C487 Group of 15th International Brigade Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938; 10640 (Item 11-0790)
  - Photo Unit #: C489 Officers of 15th International Brigade Sanidad [Health], Apr 1938; 10639 (Item 11-0791)
  - Photo Unit #: C493 Runners and Transmiciones [Transmissions], Ulldemolins, May 1938; 10638 (Item 11-1059)
  - Photo Unit #: C494 Some of the Commissariat, Tarraga, May 1938; 10637 (Item 11-1060)
  - Photo Unit #: C496 In front of 15th Brigade in Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Marca, Jun 1938; 10636 (Item 11-1061)
  - Photo Unit #: C497 Working on a car, Auto Park, Cervera, May 1938; 10635 (Item 11-1062)
  - Photo Unit #: C501 Civilians and Paul Meleschuk of Auto Park, Cervera, May 1938; 10634 (Item 11-1063)
  - Photo Unit #: C504 15th International Brigade sound truck, Codo, Aug 1938; 10633 (Item 11-1335)
  - Photo Unit #: C507 Major Germina Galleani, Bill Parker [?], Vincent Usera, Alcorisa, Jan 1938; 10632 (Item 11-0792)
  - Photo Unit #: C513 Juventud Socialista Unificada Members, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Ebro Front, May 1938; 10631 (Item 11-1064)
  - Photo Unit #: C519 Negro Machine-Gunner crew, Jun 1938; 10630 (Item 11-1065)
  - Photo Unit #: C520 Anti-aircraft unit, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jun 1938; 10629 (Item 11-1066)
  - Photo Unit #: C522 Harry Dobson, Enrique Baseto, James Bourne, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jun 1938; 10628 (Item 11-1067)
  - Photo Unit #: C523 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jun 1938; 10627 (Item 11-1068)
  - Photo Unit #: C524 Auto Park, Jun 1938; 10626 (Item 11-1069)
  - Photo Unit #: C526 Milton Wolff, [?], George Watt, [?], Lincoln-Washington, Jun 1938; 10625 (Item 11-0793)
  - Photo Unit #: C527 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jun 1938; 10624 (Item 11-0794)
  - Photo Unit #: C528 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jun 1938; 10623 (Item 11-0795)
  - Photo Unit #: C529 Joseph Brandt and Captain Milton Wolff, Lincoln-Washington, Jun 1938; 10622 (Item 11-0796)
  - Photo Unit #: C530 George Watt, Milton Wolff, Joseph Brandt, [?], Lincoln-Washington, Jun 1938; 10621 (Item 11-0379)
  - Photo Unit #: C531 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jun 1938; 10620 (Item 11-0797)
  - Photo Unit #: C532 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Jun 1938; 10619 (Item 11-0798)
  - Photo Unit #: C533 George Watt, Milton Wolff, Joseph Brandt, [?] Lincoln-Washington, Jun 1938; 10618 (Item 11-0799)
  - Photo Unit #: C539 15th International Brigade Transmiciones [Transmissions], Marca, Jun 1938; 10617 (Item 11-1070)
  - Photo Unit #: C541 15th International Brigade Transmiciones [Transmissions], wall newspaper, Jun 1938; 10616 (Item 11-1071)
  - Photo Unit #: C542 Sergants of 59th Battalion, Marca, Jun 1938; 10615 (Item 11-1072)
  - Photo Unit #: C546 Cubans in 59th Battalion, Jun 1938; 10614 (Item 11-1073)
  - Photo Unit #: C547 First aid man of Lincoln-Washington Battalion at work Marca, Jun 1938; 10613 (Item 11-1074)
  - Photo Unit #: C548 Group from base Auto Park, Alcover, Jun 1938; 10612 (Item 11-1075)
  - Photo Unit #: C553 15th International Brigade Observers, Ebro Front (Ivor Hickman, British Battalion, 3rd from right, kneeling and holding pole), Aug 1938; 10611 (Item 11-1076)
  - Photo Unit #: C554 15th International Brigade observers, Ebro Front, Aug 1938; 10610 (Item 11-1077)
  - Photo Unit #: C555 15th International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters] officers, Aug 1938; 10609 (Item 11-1078)
  - Photo Unit #: C556 James Bourne, Langston Hughes and [?], Jan 1937; 10608 (Item 11-0800)
  - Photo Unit #: C558 Martin Grumet, David Doran, undated; 10607 (Item 11-1336)
  - Photo Unit #: C564 [Group of men, some in costume], undated; 10606 (Item 11-1337)
- Series D: Miscellaneous, September 1937-June 1938; August 1938, 10355
  Series IID: Miscellaneous, September 1937 - June 1938; August 1938. The 249 images in this series include scenes of the Brigade in battlefields and at rest. Notable images include rustic cane shelters built by the Lincoln Battalion in an olive grove in Almuchel; Fascists taken prisoner at Belchite; the troops on a train from Quinto to Ambite and at a railroad station milling with civilians; soldiers in showers, washing and mending clothes, reading and playing football, and picking olives; peasants weaving; an ambulance from the Teachers Union and American Student Union with Murray Nemeroff driving; the funeral of Lieutenant William Digges at Mollerusa; the Dental Wagon with Dr. Jack Klein at work; School for Commissars at the Ebro Front; and the trial of deserters at Senes.
  - Photo Unit #: D001 Cane shelters built by Lincoln-Washington Battalion in olive grove, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10604 (Item 11-0801)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/20)
  - Photo Unit #: D002 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Headquarters, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10603 (Item 11-0802)
  - Photo Unit #: D004 Delousing machine, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10602 (Item 11-0803)
  - Photo Unit #: D005 Murray Nemeroff and Alfred Kaufman, showers and delousing, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10601 (Item 11-0804)
  - Photo Unit #: D006 Showers and delousing, Sep 1937; 10600 (Item 11-0805)
  - Photo Unit #: D007 15th International Brigade in shower machine at Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10599 (Item 11-1776)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/2)
  - Photo Unit #: D009 Showers, delousing, Sep 1937; 10598 (Item 11-1194)
  - Photo Unit #: D011 HW Dimitroff Battalion, Sep 1937; 10597 (Item 11-0806)
  - Photo Unit #: D014 Chess, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10596 (Item 11-0807)
  - Photo Unit #: D015 Hamburger Boys, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10595 (Item 11-0808)
  - Photo Unit #: D017 Vladimir Copic addressing Dimitroff Battalion prior to their leaving to join 13th International Brigade, Oct 1937; 10594 (Item 11-0809)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/6)
  - Photo Unit #: D018 Lieutenant Colonal Vladimir Copic addressing Dimitroff Battalion prior to their leaving to join 13th, Oct 1937; 10593 (Item 11-1338)
  - Photo Unit #: D019 Meeting of Dimitroff Battalion the night before they joined the 13th International Brigade, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10592 (Item 11-1786)
  - Photo Unit #: D023 F. O'Brien of British Battalion with Anastasia [?], son of president of CP and editor of local party paper at Modejar, Senes, Oct 1937; 10591 (Item 11-1339)
  - Photo Unit #: D026 Presentation of awards to comrade Michael Zajac, Senes, Oct 1937; 10590 (Item 11-0810)
  - Photo Unit #: D029 Colonel Stephen Fuqua at 15th International Brigade in Quinto (American Military Attache); Captain Hans Amlie (l.), Robert Merriman, Robert Thompson, David Doran and Colonel Fuqua, Oct 1937; 10589 (Item 11-0811)
  - Photo Unit #: D032 Colonel Stephen Fuqua and David Doran in trenches at Fuentes, Quinto, Oct 1937; 10588 (Item 11-1340)
  - Photo Unit #: D033 Colonel Stephen Fuqua (l.) and David Doran in trenches at Fuentes, Quinto, Oct 1937; 10587 (Item 11-0812)
    (Moscow Number: 5/195/2)
  - Photo Unit #: D035 Street, 15th International Brigade Headquarters, Quinto, Oct 1937; 10586 (Item 11-0813)
  - Photo Unit #: D037 15th International Brigade moving pictures by Herbert Kline (probably in Quinto), October 1937. Far left, Henri Cartier-Bresson; foreground, facing camera, Jacques Lemare., Oct 1937; 10585 (Item 11-0814)
  - Photo Unit #: D038 (During fiming of) 15th International Brigade moving pictures by Herbert Kline; Herber Kline is center, with satchel over his right shoulder, back to camera., Oct 1937; 10584 (Item 11-0815)
  - Photo Unit #: D039 Captain Hans Amlie and Colonel Stephen Fuqua, Oct 1937; 10583 (Item 11-0816)
  - Photo Unit #: D040 Colonel Stephen Fuqua and Captain Hans Amlie, Oct 1937; 10582 (Item 11-0817)
  - Photo Unit #: D041 [Filming] at Quinto: [Jaques Lemare, Henri Cartier-Bresson, and Herbert Kline], Oct 1937; 10581 (Item 11-0818)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/23)
  - Photo Unit #: D044 Trial of deserters, Senes, Oct 1937; 10580 (Item 11-0819)
  - Photo Unit #: D050 Evacuation of civilians from Codo [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Sep 1937; 369374 (Item 11-1891)
  - Photo Unit #: D052 Colonel Stephen Fuqua (l.) and Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Quinto, Oct 1937; 10579 (Item 11-0820)
  - Photo Unit #: D053 Colonel Stephen Fuqua (l.) and Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Quinto, Oct 1937; 10578 (Item 11-0821)
  - Photo Unit #: D054 Colonel Stephen Fuqua, David Doran, and Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Oct 1937; 10577 (Item 11-0822)
  - Photo Unit #: D055 Colonel Stephen Fuqua (l.) and Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Quinto, Oct 1937; 10576 (Item 11-0823)
  - Photo Unit #: D056 David Doran, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Colonel Stephen Fuqua, Captain Hans Amlie, Major Robert Merriman, Oct 1937; 10575 (Item 11-0824)
    (Moscow Number: 5/195/9)
  - Photo Unit #: D057 David Doran, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Colonel Stephen Fuqua, Major Robert Merriman, Oct 1937; 10574 (Item 11-0825)
  - Photo Unit #: D058 Major Robert Merriman, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, Colonel Stephen Fuqua, Captain Hans Amlie, Oct 1937; 10573 (Item 11-0826)
  - Photo Unit #: D059 Trip from Quinto to Ambite, Nov 1937; 10572 (Item 11-0827)
  - Photo Unit #: D060 Lincoln-Washington kitchen on trip from Quinto to Ambite, Nov 1937; 10571 (Item 11-1341)
  - Photo Unit #: D062 Lincoln-Washington kitchen on trip from Quinto to Ambite, Nov 1937; 10570 (Item 11-0828)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/76)
  - Photo Unit #: D063 Lincoln-Washington kitchen on trip from Quinto to Ambite, Nov 1937; 10569 (Item 11-1342)
  - Photo Unit #: D064 Lincoln-Washington kitchen on trip from Quinto to Ambite, getting water, Nov 1937; 10568 (Item 11-0829)
  - Photo Unit #: D066 Trip from Quinto to Ambite, Nov 1937; 10567 (Item 11-0830)
  - Photo Unit #: D067 Boarding side-door Pullmans after morning coffee, Quinto-Ambite, Nov 1937; 10566 (Item 11-1768)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/72)
  - Photo Unit #: D068 Rain in camp, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10565 (Item 11-0831)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/80)
  - Photo Unit #: D069 Rain in camp, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10564 (Item 11-0832)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/77)
  - Photo Unit #: D070 Rain in camp, Almuchel, Sep 1937; 10563 (Item 11-0833)
  - Photo Unit #: D072 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite, Nov 1937; 10562 (Item 11-1767)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/71)
  - Photo Unit #: D073 Train at Quinto-Ambite, Nov 1937; 10561 (Item 11-1765)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/69)
  - Photo Unit #: D075 Kitchen on train, Quinto-Ambite, Nov 1937; 10560 (Item 11-1770)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/75)
  - Photo Unit #: D077 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite, Nov 1937; 10559 (Item 11-1766)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/70)
  - Photo Unit #: D078 Train ride from Quinto to Ambite [scene of villagers and houses], Nov 1937; 10558 (Item 11-1343)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/78)
  - Photo Unit #: D079 [?], [?] and Murray Nemeroff on train from Quinto to Abite, Nov 1937; 10557 (Item 11-0834)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/28)
  - Photo Unit #: D080 Train trip from Quinto to Ambite, Nov 1937; 10556 (Item 11-0835)
  - Photo Unit #: D081 Train trip from Quinto to Ambite, Nov 1937; 10555 (Item 11-0836)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/74)
  - Photo Unit #: D082 Quarters of English Battalion at Andujar, Nov 1937; 10554 (Item 11-1795)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/6)
  - Photo Unit #: D083 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite, Nov 1937; 10553 (Item 11-1769)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/73)
  - Photo Unit #: D085 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite [duplicate of 11_1775], Nov 1937; 10552 (Item 11-1772)
    Available Formats: Copy Negative; Moscownegative
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/79)
  - Photo Unit #: D085 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite [duplicate of 11_1772], Nov 1937; 10551 (Item 11-1775)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/82)
  - Photo Unit #: D086 Train ride, Quinto-Ambite [soldiers with gear, lying on or near tracks], Nov 1937; 10550 (Item 11-1773)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/80)
  - Photo Unit #: D088 Battalion Headquarters, Mendejar [3 men sitting on ground, reading the Daily Worker], Nov 1937; 10549 (Item 11-1344)
  - Photo Unit #: D089 English Battalion Headquarters at Mondejar, Nov 1937; 10548 (Item 11-1195)
  - Photo Unit #: D090 Civilians and soldiers at siding during train ride, Quinto-Ambite, Nov 1937; 10547 (Item 11-1771)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/77)
  - Photo Unit #: D091 ? with (l) Fred Mattersdorfer, (r) Einiv Junkala [Soldier playing guitar, seated in a boxcar door. Poster on exterior of car], Nov 1937; 10546 (Item 11-1345)
  - Photo Unit #: D094 Comrades with a flag captured in Quinto, Sep 1937; 10545 (Item 11-0260)
    (Moscow Number: 5/191/13)
  - Photo Unit #: D095 [3] Lincoln Brigade members on road to Saragossa about 15 km away, undated; 10544 (Item 11-1346)
  - Photo Unit #: D097 School in Quinto, Nov 1937; 10543 (Item 11-1079)
  - Photo Unit #: D098 Soldiers and civilians at railroad station, train ride from Quinto-Ambite, Nov 1937; 10542 (Item 11-1774)
    (Moscow Number: 5/180/81)
  - Photo Unit #: D099 Langston Hughes (l.) and Crawford Morgan [with bandaged hand] at Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10541 (Item 11-1347)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/19)
  - Photo Unit #: D100 Langston Hughes (l.) and Crawford Morgan at Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10540 (Item 11-0837)
  - Photo Unit #: D101 Crawford Morgan (l.), [?] Markowitz, [?] Parker and Langston Hughes, Oct 1937; 10539 (Item 11-0838)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/7)
  - Photo Unit #: D102 Langston Hughes, Quinto - Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937; 10538 (Item 11-0839)
  - Photo Unit #: D104 Nurse Lillian Armstan, Oct 1937; 10537 (Item 11-0840)
  - Photo Unit #: D106 Nurse Irene Goldin, Oct 1937; 10536 (Item 11-0841)
  - Photo Unit #: D107 Fiesta in Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro, [crowded street, soldiers on balcony with flag], Oct 1937; 10535 (Item 11-1780)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/9)
  - Photo Unit #: D108 Fiesta in Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro [outdoors, crowd listening to a piano-player], Oct 1937; 10534 (Item 11-1348)
    Available Formats: Copy NegativePrint; Moscow negative
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/5)
  - Photo Unit #: D110 English anti-tank battery at rest, Ambite, Nov 1937; 10533 (Item 11-1796)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/7)
  - Photo Unit #: D111 English anti-tank battery at rest, Ambite; [soldier playing a recorder], Nov 1937; 10532 (Item 11-1800)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/12)
  - Photo Unit #: D113 Major Modeste at 15th Brigade, Ambite, Nov 1937; 10531 (Item 11-1349)
  - Photo Unit #: D114 Major Modesto at 15th Brigade at Ambite, Nov 1937; 10530 (Item 11-1080)
    (Moscow Number: 5/175/7)
  - Photo Unit #: D115 Major Juan Modesto at 15th International Brigade at Ambite, Nov 1937; 10529 (Item 11-1755)
    (Moscow Number: 5/175/6)
  - Photo Unit #: D116 Major Modesto at 15th Brigade at Ambite, Nov 1937; 10528 (Item 11-1081)
    (Moscow Number: 5/175/8)